I'm not paying $500 to get my locks done.
When I was going to my loctician in Harlem, I was paying her $4.50.
I was paying to take an Uber to the train station and from the train station because there was nowhere for me to park in Harlem.
I was also paying to take the train to Harlem.
So we've gone now from $4.50 to, that's $7.50, so I don't do math.
So we're around $5.50 at this point.
Plus, I will board my dog for the day so he's not sitting at home.
So that's $50.
So now we're at $600 and I will buy her lunch.
And in this moment, I'm realizing I'm going to just learn how to do my locks myself because I was doing all of that.
And then she even flip-moded on me.
That's her own issue, you know, sending her love and light that she finds the way to get through that.
But in this moment, I realize I'm going to learn how to do my locks myself or at least I'm going to try to learn first.
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to try first.